Guide to the Herbert Matter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4: Graphic Design Projects, 71.5 linear ft.
  - Subseries 4.19: Negatives
    - Subsubseries 4.19.01: General
      - Container Corporation of America (CCA); Ink and water; Lee Krasner;Steps; Fly., b/w 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 165, Folder 8)
      - PLUS (magazine supplement, Architectural forum)., b/w 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 165, Folder 9)
      - Magic Mountain - Londonderry, Vermont., Color and b/w 2 1/4: 8x10 negatives (Othertype 165, Folder 10)
        Publicity for ski resort.
      - New York 1939 World's Fair Swiss Pavilion [1 of 4]., b/w 2 1/4: 4x5: 5x7: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 1)
      - New York 1939 World's Fair Swiss Pavilion [2 of 4]., b/w 2 1/4: 4x5: 5x7: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 2)
      - New York 1939 World's Fair Swiss Pavilion [3 of 4]., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 3)
        Cover ofKoralle magazine. Caption says "Kuhne Flugspiele eines Piloten, orOne bold pilot plays in flight.
      - New York 1939 World's Fair Swiss Pavilion [4 of 4]., b/w 5x7 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 4)
        Model for plexiglass.
      - Fortune [1 of 2]., b/w 2 1/4: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 5)
      - Fortune [2 of 2]., b/w 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 6)
      - Joel and DePalma., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 7)
      - Portraits of Cassandre., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 8)
      - Portraits of Joan Crawford., Color 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 9)
      - Portraits of Paulette Goddard., b/w 35 mm: 2 1/4 negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 10)
      - Portraits of Franz Klein and de Kooning (New York Studio School)., b/w 35 mm negatives. (Othertype 166, Folder 11)
        Klein, Franz; de Kooning, Willem
      - Technology Square., b/w 8x10 negatives with colored hand blocking. (Othertype 167, Folder 2)
      - Boston Main Railroad (BMRR)., b/w 8x10 negatives with colored hand blocking. (Othertype 167, Folder 3)
      - Hew Haven Railroad (NHRR); One with Cummins Engine Company on same negative., b/w 8x10 negatives with colored hand blocking. (Othertype 167, Folder 4)
      - Wyandotte Chemicals Corp., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 167, Folder 5)
      - Colonial Williamsburg (book)., b/w 4x5: 2 1/4 negatives. (Othertype 167, Folder 6)
      - Carlo Picchetti - Fontana Di Rome; holiday card., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 167, Folder 7)
      - Oxford Paper., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 167, Folder 8)
      - Catalog of Games 1967., Color 2 1/4 transparencies. (Othertype 167, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified client (baseball gloves)., b/w 8x10 negatives. Includes (2) with red color dye applied to negative surface: outlining glove. (Othertype 168, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified client (industrial machinery)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified client (linotype)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified client (ice cubes)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 4)
      - Unidentified client (coins)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 5)
      - Unidentified client (fog - experimental)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified client (swirl - experimental)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified client (Mother Goose)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified client (weathervane)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified client (constructed wooden "box" interior pattern)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified clients (chair; drawer set)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified clients (flowers with shadow)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 12)
      - Unidentified clients (fonts)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 168, Folder 13)
      - Unidentified client (Bernardo Sandals)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified client (Robert Clark; Amy Lownds - lampshades)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified client (circular shape with shadows); Shadows of glass objects on table., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified client (galaxy image from a book)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Unidentified client (rounded vessel shapes with tops)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Unidentified client (off-shore rig/station)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified client (pillow/cylinder in motion)., b/w 2 1/4 strips. (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified client (two people atDavidson machinery)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified client (abstract repetitive image with string)., b/w 7x9 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified client (circles;Wasser tropten)., b/w 7x9 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified client (butterflies)., b/w 7x9 negatives: assorted cut sizes. (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified client (horizontal abstract image)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 12)
      - Unidentified client (German playing cardsSpielkarten)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 13)
      - Unidentified client (children;repro fin poster peshalloofi)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified client (couple surveying on high cliff)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - Unidentified client (negative of negative of extreme close-up of face)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Unidentified client (French seal with sun; star)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - Unidentified client (abstract water with glass schweiber berge duplicate)., b/w 7x9 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 18)
      - Unidentified client (moon with German text)., b/w 7x9 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 19)
      - Unidentified client (artwork - French town painting depicting town center)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 20)
      - Unidentified client (artwork - Last Judgment)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified client (child and duck)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 22)
      - Unidentified client (bust with damaged nose)., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 169, Folder 23)
      - Unidentified client (cross-section of shell)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 24)
      - Unidentified client (flat tree leaf - extreme close-up)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 25)
      - Unidentified client (flat tree leaf )., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 26)
      - Unidentified client (water abstract)., b/w and blue toner: 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 27)
      - Unidentified client (serpent - warrior artwork)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 28)
      - Unidentified client (sea and sky)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 29)
      - Unidentified client (numbers; sequenced dots)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 30)
      - Unidentified client (sphere with degree angles)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 31)
      - Unidentified client (moon phases)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 32)
      - Unidentified client (low furniture tables - studio)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 33)
      - Unidentified client (Cognitronics transistors)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 34)
      - Unidentified client (abacus)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 35)
      - Unidentified client (atomic structure - spherical).., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 36)
      - Unidentified client (world)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 37)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified older man with violin)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 38)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified man with violin)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 39)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified woman with violin)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 40)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified pianist at home)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 41)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified orchestra leader)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 42)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified musician at home with family)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 43)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified trainPresident Lincoln; New Jersey)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 44)
      - Unidentified client (artwork - paintings; unidentified)., b/w cut to 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 45)
      - Unidentified client (Yale)., b/w 35 mm: 4x5 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 46)
        Includes Yale art gallery under construction.
      - Unidentified client (Le Corbusier paintings)., b/w 2 1/4: 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 47)
      - Unidentified client (unidentified Eugene Ormandy)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 48)
      - Unidentified client (Jessica Dragonette)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 49)
      - Unidentified client (eagle; squirrels)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 50)
      - Unidentified client (Kauffman Saddles)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 51)
      - Unidentified client (man in recording studio)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 52)
      - Unidentified client (Art - pencil drawings of woman; baby; landscape)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 53)
      - Unidentified client (Paul Rudolph)., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 54)
      - Unidentified client (Art - unidentified biblical and figure sketches from art book)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 169, Folder 55)
      - Fashion., b/w 2 1/4: 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 171)
        Glamour. Harper's Bazaar. Lady's Home Journal. Collier's. Vogue. Bride's Magazine. House Beautiful. Life. Mademoiselle. Bermuda used for Bride's Magazine.Vogue issue August 1943.Vogue jewelry.Harper's Bazaar Mount Tremblant.Coca-Cola 1939 (not accepted).Euka Rayon 1939.Betsy Zogbaum.Bride's Magazine 1941.Raincoats for Harper's Bazaar 1937.Boys' Heads 1942.Bride's Magazine 1940.Stetson hats.Hats for Yardley.
      - Fashion., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 172)
        Glamour. Harper's Bazaar. Lady's Home Journal. Collier's. Vogue. Bride's Magazine. House Beautiful. Life. Mademoiselle. Fashion experiments. Conde Nast 1948 abstracts.
        Conde Nast Publications, inc.
      - Fashion., Color 2 1/4: 4x5 negatives. (Othertype 173)
        Yardley. Mrs. Ross for Hearts High. Farnsworth. Laurie Douglas (wearing Calder jewelry). Betty MacLandlem (?).
      - Fashion., b/w 2 1/4: 120 mm: 35 mm: 4x5 negatives. (Box 174)
        Glamour. Harper's Bazaar (1942). Lady's Home Journal. Collier's (1937). Vogue (1947). Bride's Magazine. House Beautiful (1936). Life (1936, 1938, 1939). Mademoiselle (1939). Saks Fifth Avenue (1937). Sun Cream (1938). Lincoln Zephry (1937). Pictoral Revue (1937, 1938). - Children in garden - for House Beautiful, 1936. - Young girl in Central Park - 1938.- Bathing suit - for Harper's Bazaar, 1938. - Furs, fur coats - for Mademoiselle, 1939. - Foxes - for Harper's Bazaar, 1939.- Gloves, Arden Laura Douglas - for Vogue, 1938. (?) - Lincoln Continental - for Vogue. - Central Park skier- Skier costumes - for Mademoiselle, 1939. - Virginia - for Bride's.
      - Unidentified clients; Fashion experiments., Color 8x10 negatives (some cut: mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 1)
      - Container Corporation of America;Ingenious Packaging 1958; geometric pattern with colored "box"ed., Color 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 2)
      - Fortune., Color 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 3)
      - Oxford Paper., Color 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 4)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation., b/w 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 5)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation., Color 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified clients (AB X)., Color 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified clients (AB X letters)., b/w 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified clients (cross-section of shell)., b/w 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified clients (flat tree leaf)., b/w 8x10 negatives (mounted). (Othertype 176, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified clients; Fabric (various)., Color 2 1/4: 8x10 and b/w 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 182)
      - History of Writing., Color 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Othertype 199, Folder 1)
      - Duchamp-Villon; Masters of Modern Art book., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Antione Pevsner; Masters of Modern Art book., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Zorach; Masters of Modern Art book; p; 107., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Arp; Masters of Modern Art book page 140., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Henry Moore; Masters of Modern Art book; page 148., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Julio Gonzalez; Masters of Modern Art book., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Wilhelm Lehmbruck; Masters of Modern Art book., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Laurens; Masters of Modern Art book; page 78., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [1 of 7]., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [2 of 7]., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 10)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [3 of 7]., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 11)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [4 of 7]., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 12)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [5 of 7]., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 13)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [6 of 7]., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 14)
      - Masters of Modern Art book [7 of 7]., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Box 213, Folder 15)
      - Brancusi, Constantin; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 1)
      - DeStijl; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 2)
      - Le Corbusier; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 3)
      - Art Nouveau Guimard desk; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 4)
      - Graphic design collection (posters); Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 5)
      - Glass and porcelain objects; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 6)
      - Chrome; steel objects; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 7)
      - Tableware; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 8)
      - Machines (typewriter; radio; adding machine); Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 9)
      - Metal kitchenware; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 10)
      - Cutlery; serving pieces; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 11)
      - Kitchen objects; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 12)
      - Dinnerware; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 13)
      - Modern chair collection; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 14)
      - Frederick Kiesler; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 15)
      - Paul Nelson; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 16)
      - Mies van der Rohe; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 17)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright; Masters of Modern Art book., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 229, Folder 18)
      - Unidentified artwork - cut-up montage., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - MOMA (Museum of Modern Art) Monroe Wheeler desk., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 2)
        Wheeler, Monroe
      - Unidentified client - fabric., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified client - 18th and 19th century residential artifacts - studio., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust., Color 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - DeBeers., Color 4x5 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 6)
      - Fashion experiments (Conde Nast 1948) - abstracts [1 of 3]., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 7)
      - Fashion experiments (Conde Nast 1948) - abstracts [2 of 3]., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 8)
      - Fashion experiments (Conde Nast 1948) - abstracts [3 of 3]., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified client - leaf fabric., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified client - fabric on table., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 11)
      - Farnsworth television., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 12)
      - Crushed paper/foil., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 13)
      - Fashion model in profile., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 14)
      - House and Garden flowers., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 15)
      - Poster by Whelans, b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 16)
      - Little, John., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 234, Folder 17)
      - Cummins Engine Company (trade show model); [Folder 1 of 2]., Color 8x10 transparencies. (Othertype 264, Folder 1)
      - Cummins Engine Company (trade show model); [Folder 2 of 2]., Color 2 1/4 color negatives mounted on black boards. (Othertype 264, Folder 2)
      - Art - Lee Bontecou., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Bucher (books)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 2)
        Includes note handwritten by Matter.
      - Art in Our Time (art book)., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 3)
        Studio photos of finished book.
      - Model for Exposition - U.S. Housing Project., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - EamesChristmas balls Charlie., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - Pierre Matisse portrait., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 6)
      - Lucia Eames with bow and arrow., b/w 2 1/4: half frame negatives. (Box 383, Folder 7)
      - Arts and Architecture building plans for construction center., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 8)
      - Arts and Architecture., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 9)
      - Ray Eames artwork., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 10)
      - Telephone; parked cars., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 11)
      - Phonograph with swing record., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 12)
      - Musical instruments., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 13)
      - Dondel artwork., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 14)
      - James Johnson Sweeney apartment., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 15)
      - Skier., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 17)
      - Carles artwork., b/w 2 1/4: 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 18)
      - Mondrian artwork., b/w 4x5: 8x10 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 19)
      - EamesEvans Radio Cabinet., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 20)
      - Doris Knox in Eames' tilt-back chair., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified woman portrait., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 22)
      - EamesCharles furniture drawing and wood grain., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 23)
      - Eames property (vacant lot)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 24)
      - Eames plywood airplane wings., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 25)
      - Art from Museum of Fine Arts, Houston., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 26)
      - Exhibition catalog and book designs for Guggenheim Museum., b/w 8x10 transparencies. (Box 383, Folder 26)
      - Guggenheim Museum interior., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 383, Folder 27)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation.ND, b/w 8x10 transparencies (Box 411, Folder 1)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation; [Folder 1 of 3].ND, color 8x10 transparencies (Box 411, Folder 2)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation; [Folder 2 of 3].ND, color 8x10 transparencies (Box 411, Folder 3)
      - Wyandotte Chemical Corporation; [Folder 3 of 3].ND, color 8x10 transparencies (Box 411, Folder 4)
      - Oxford Paper.ND, b/w 8x10 negatives (Box 411, Folder 5)
      - Unidentified Chinese puppets., color 8x10 negatives (Othertype 413)
      - Jackson Pollock drawing., b/w 8x10 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 1)
      - Jackson Pollock painting., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 2)
      - Jackson Pollock paintings., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 3)
      - Wood on Jackson Pollock property., Color 2 1/4 transparancies, b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 4)
      - Jackson Pollock painting., color 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 5)
      - Lee Krasner's mosaic table., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 6)
      - Harry Bertoia drawings., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 7)
      - Willelm de Kooning in studio., color 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 8)
        de Kooning, Willem
      - Rockefeller at night; Sparse trees and snow on ground., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 9)
      - Candelabra with melted wax., color 8x10 negative mounted on a poster frame. (Box 436, Folder 10)
      - Woman fashion model with American flag., color 8x10 negative. (Box 436, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified clients; flat tree leafs., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 12)
      - Alexander Stirling Calder sculptures., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 13)
      - New York City rooftop., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified woman painting mural., b/w 4x5 negative. (Box 436, Folder 15)
      - Jackson Pollock in front of mural (two variations)., b/w 4x5 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 16)
      - Jackson Pollock paintings at Art of the Century., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 19)
      - Fernand Leger at New York World's Fair, 1939., b/w 2 1/4 negatives. (Box 436, Folder 20)
        Leger, Fernanc
      - Jackson Pollock portrait at Art of the Century., b/w half-frame negatives. (Box 436, Folder 21)
    - Subsubseries 4.19.02: Universal Limited Art Editions
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Schlossberg, Edwin., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Announcement letter 1972., negatives: color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Marisol., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Rivers, Larry; Southern, Terry., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Fuller, Buckminster;Tetrascroll., negatives: b/w 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Johns, Jasper [Folder 1 of 2]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Johns, Jasper [Folder 2 of 2]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; O' Hara, Frank; Rivers, Larry., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Frankenthaler, Helen., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Bontecou, Lee., negatives: b/w 8x10 (Box 324)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Motherwell, Robert [Folder 1 of 3]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 325)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Motherwell, Robert [Folder 2 of 3]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 325)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Motherwell, Robert [Folder 3 of 3]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 325)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Twombly, Cy., negatives: b/w 8x10 (Box 325)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Rauschenberg, Robert [Folder 1 of 2]., negatives: b/w and color 8x10 (Box 325)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions; Rauschenberg, Robert [Folder 2 of 2]., negatives: color 8x10 (Box 325)